# Cihangir Bozdogan

London bozdogan.cihangir@gmail.com +44 7342759900

Another web developer, based in London. Nowadays I'm mostly focused on development but I like to design and explore new visual trends. 7 years of experience in programming and over 9 years experience in print and digital graphic design. I have theoretical knowledge as well as hands-on practical experience of developing designs for fully interactive and responsive websites.

# Work Experience

#### Cofounder

Monitorables January 2021 to Present

Monitorables is an online market research store aiming specifically at e-commerce industry. I involved marketing and handling the business side of the things as well as maintaining the website.

### **Web Developer**

Social Swag Digital Agency - London June 2015 to October 2020

Social Swag is a digital marketing company which focuses on creating content for the web. My duty was maintaining their custom built content management platform. Building new features, fixing bugs, improving the codebase. Often I would design and code banners and landing pages for their old clients.

Technologies (After 2018): Firebase, TypeScript, React, Sass, Git, Github, Figma. Technologies (Before 2018): Laravel, Vue, Mysql, Sass, Git, Github, Figma.

#### **Web Developer**

Salon Guru - London January 2015 to February 2016

Building websites, landing pages, html emails, creating social media posts, banners and handling graphic design work.

Technologies: Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Wordpress, MySql, Cpanel, Photoshop, Illustrator, MailChimp.

#### **Web Developer**

Master Legal Services - London November 2014 to June 2015

Maintaining company's Wordpress website, social

media, Google analytics, email marketing, SEO and graphic design.

Technologies: Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Wordpress, Cpanel, Photoshop, Illustrator.

# Education

# Bachelor's in computer drafting and design

European University of Lefke - Lefke July 2011 to September 2013

## A-Level or equivalent in Electrical technician

Yildirim Technology College - Ankara October 2008 to June 2012

## Skills

- Git
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- React
- Php
- Sql
- vue
- Linux
- HTML5
- Jquery
- Node.js
- Redux
- Nextjs
- Typescript
- Nuxt
- Sass
- Javascript
- CSS
- Responsive Web Design

# Languages

- English Fluent
- Turkish Fluent

## Links

https://github.com/jankoboz/

https://uk.linkedin.com/in/cihangir-bozdogan-63459035